For now, it doesn't look like
anyone's trying to tail us.
Bucerati, shouldn't we be leaving Venice?
The boss commands a convoy of bodyguards.
Chances are they already know
about our betraying the Family.
The next threat will likely turn
out to be someone from the inside.
The worst part is, we have no idea
what kind of torture they can dole out.
Certo.
It's far too risky for our band
of defectors to take to the seas.
For now, we observe.
Understood.
Mister!
We're hungry!
Hey, what are you waiting for?
Feed us!
My guts are free!
What's with the hold up?
Where's the food?
Enough!
I hate to ask this right now, but do you
think we have time to drop by a restaurant?
I suppose we do.
Okay, then.
We should all fill our goat sauce.
Let's go.
Thank you
so
much for watching.
So, I was thinking, people that
are vegan, do they eat cheese?
Or does it, like, go against
one of their rules or something?
Uh, I'm pretty positive that they don't.
Products like milk and eggs come
from cows and chickens, remember?
And since you put milk in a cake,
that's a Naoko as well. Wait, what?
They have to swear off cake too?
I wonder if all that health crap
really makes any difference.
So nothing from animals?
Then what do they do
about shoes or handbags?
All of that stuff is made
from leather, isn't it?
Look, they're vegan because
they feel bad for the animals.
They wear sneakers and carry
around backpacks instead.
Oh man!
They take this stuff so seriously!
So are there a bunch of vegan grannies
out there dressed like ballplayers?
Hey Giorno, fear won't do us any favors.
Try to relax and eat.
Sure, I'll try to, but we
all need to remain vigilant.
If not, someone could
easily poison our food.
Huh?
The hell are you doing,
you spindly little shit?!
What the...?
You think I'm gonna let
you get away with this?
This stain is gonna cost you!
My suit cost four million lira, pal!
Now I'm gonna make you pay!
So you're our next foe! What?
Don't hear you!
You trying to start trouble?
Take that, Katsune! And this! And this!
And one of these!
Hey, pump the brakes for a second.
I don't think this guy's an enemy.
He's out cold.
A random citizen. Go figure. What?
Are you for real?
Oh, shit, what am I gonna do now?
Yeah, sucks for you, but this
stain's not going anywhere.
Guess that's what happens when you mess
up and spill red wine on a white suit.
No way!
I can pay for something this fancy!
Putting a button there
should cover it up nicely,
so good thing for you
the stain is where it is.
Before we let this guy go?
Let's have them taste our food for poison!
Enough, we don't have
time to mess around now.
Something's not right?
What in the world is
going on with Bucciarati?
There's no question about it.
His heart was stopped after
his battle with the boss.
And when he pierced his hand?
Not a single drop of blood
seeped from the wound.
This whole thing is so confusing!
But this really isn't
the time to investigate.
gate, since it's still just a feeling.
Letting the others know
wouldn't do any good.
Okay, Bucciarati.
What do we do from here on out?
The boss possesses the
power to obliterate time,
and only he can move when his ability
is activated.
He is unstoppable.
Doesn't matter the person or the approach.
His stand
is so powerful, attacks
have no effect in the least.
However...
All bets are off once
we unveil his identity.
After we finally figure
out who the boss really is,
we can eliminate him once and for all.
It'll be tough, but we've no other choice.
It's kill or be killed.
I'm with you, but how the
hell are we gonna find him?
The boss has made extra certain to
remove any trace of his life till now.
What about Trish?
Surely we can learn something useful
from her, given how involved she is.
Just think about how those goons
and the boss came after her.
You know?
Well, I've been thinking.
I don't like it.
We've already involved
Trish enough in this.
It just doesn't feel right.
Trish is the true victim here.
Knowing her own father tried to kill her.
Think how she must be feeling.
It's too much.
Have a heart, Bucciarati.
Involving her in the hunt for the boss
and his secret identity is the wrong move!
Thank you.
But it's okay, Narancia.
I've known all that.
About the kind of man he is.
My father.
T-Trish.
No, it's alright.
In fact, your talk of him leaving
no trace sparked something.
I wondered about my father.
So I asked Mom, and she said
she met him in Sardinia.
Sardinia.
When I was little, Mom told a story
that was very strange to me at the time.
They met while she was on vacation.
One day, he went to run an errand.
But he vanished and left nothing behind.
Not even his real name.
That must have been right
before he became the boss.
That far back, do you think
it could be his hometown?
I can't say for sure.
But, it's somewhere to start.
Sardinia holds the key
to his past and identity.
You know what telling us that means?
We very well might end up
killing your biological father.
No, we'll do all we can to bring him down.
Honestly, whether your group decides to
kill him or not is your own business.
There's only one thing I want to know,
and it's whose blood is
coursing through my veins!
I'll be damned if someone kills
me before I get an answer!
Look at that, Narancia.
Guess you were wrong.
This girl standing before us is way
tougher than you thought she was.
Fine, I get it.
Sardinia...
That's where we're heading
after we escape this place.
It's where we'll find out
who the boss really is.
Guess I was projecting too much onto
Trish and totally missed the mark.
It's clear she's already
found her Determinazione.
But given that I decided to join
this suicide mission on a whim,
I'm going into this thing with
more doubt than hope for now.
Ah Uh, guys, we've got company!
My soup's got a weird
shark swimming in it!
Lil' Bomber!
Jean, quick!
Get Trish inside the turtle!
Habakio, guard right! Mista, left!
Well, where are they?
Where are we being attacked from?
Inside the soup bowl.
I don't know how it got in there, though.
Are you serious?
But it was right there!
I swear there was some
shark-looking thing in my soup!
Huh?
I'm not seeing anything strange here.
Did we lose the thing already?
Narancia, you okay?
What happened?
What the heck are you screaming about?
What?
Did that shark bite you?
Tell me what's wrong.
I can help. Talk to me!
I'm trying to help, but
you gotta answer me!
Hold on a moment, Mista.
Narancia may not be able to speak.
What?
Have you really lost your voice?
What's wrong, Narancia?
Just what are you pointing at?
Is it the water?
You want a drink of that?
Hey, guys, we're gonna
need some help over here.
Look, his tongue has been
ripped right out of his mouth.
I don't think he's breathing either.
This isn't good.
I can make a replacement for
his tongue using Golden Wind,
but it'll take a little time to do it.
We don't have time.
Can't you see that Naranj
is about to suffocate?
Mista, do you have a pen on you?
Pen?
Yeah, it's right here, but
what do you need it for?
Oh man, that was close.
I'll imbue the pen with life force
and create the replacement tissue.
That way, he'll be able to
breathe through the process.
It all makes sense now.
That's Giorno Giovanna.
This is very interesting indeed, and
it explains the boss's intel reports.
So the greatest threat to the Family
comes from this cannoli-haired,
deadbeat newcomer. Yeah.
I have to admit, the brat keeping
Narancia alive was a surprise.
Never in my wildest dreams
would I have imagined Crush
having any trouble with this
particular assassination.
But apparently killing all
five of these reprobates
will necessitate your
involvement as well, Tiziano.
As the boss's elite guard, it is our duty
to ensure these turncoats perish here.
Are you ready to do what
must be done, Squalo?
Do you even need to ask?
Once I lure them into the water,
Crush will be unstoppable.
Our plan will decide everything.
Let's offer them one by one, Tiziano.
Gladly, Squalo.
And our friend Narancia is going to help.
Are you alright, Narancia? I'm good.
That was close.
What info can you give us?
Who are they?
How does their stand work?
It was in the soup bowl.
Some kind of shark.
Narancia, try to relax.
I'm fine. I can talk.
Hey, help us out.
What does the enemy look like?
Which way did he go?
He was...
He was really small, like a huge pebble!
And he ran into the
back of the restaurant!
It was crazy!
Huh?
How can a pebble be huge?
Weren't you saying just a few minutes
ago that you found it in your soup?
You're not making any sense.
What?
No, I didn't really say that, did I?
Here, answer this for me.
Would you say our foe's
about yay, Big? Nuh-uh.
No, wait, I...
Then would you say it's about this, Big?
It's bigger, so you're saying
it's something like this.
Yeah, you got it.
So this big-ass enemy was
taking a dip in your bowl,
then they just ran off into
the restaurant and vanished?
Mm-hmm. What the?
Why are they...
Sorry, but we're not quite understanding
the picture you're trying to paint.
You mean...
they move at extremely high speeds? No!
They're as slow as you can be!
Say what? Come on!
If it was as huge and slow as you
say, then why didn't we see it?
You sure you really saw Stan Narancia?
Of course I did!
Not see one!
Huh?
You're starting to
sound like a real wacko.
Hang on.
You're not trying to hide the fact that
you got beat by the enemy, are you?
Come out with it already.
You didn't see a damn thing, did you?
Of course I did.
Well, which is it?
Did you really see
something or didn't you?
You picked a hell of a
time to take a round.
I don't sense anything nearby.
Whatever it is, it's
probably a long-range stand.
And if you're right about that, the
user must be observing from afar.
Come, we need to go.
I have a feeling our escape
should be sooner than later.
The canal will take us out to sea.
That's a great idea, Giorno!
Let's get going!
The canal's waiting for us to take out!
Yes, Narancia.
Thanks for reiterating that.
Narancia?
What's going on?
Why are you covering your mouth like that?
Is there a problem?
Show us whatever it is you're hiding!
I'm not seeing anything.
Yep, nothing to see here.
There's absolutely nothing wrong.
Nothing at all.
So, what now, Bucerati?
Are we all going to head out to sea?
No, we're not heading
down the canal just yet.
This is our chance, men.
Our chance to hunt down
and eliminate the enemy.
Luckily, the boss never saw
our little betrayal coming.
He has sentries everywhere,
but it's safe to say he hasn't had time
to mobilize all his forces. Meaning,
if we take down this foe, we'll be able
to escape to the sea much more safely.
You know what?
That makes a lot of sense. I'm all in.
Yeah, you can count me in too.
Then it's all settled.
Pucerati, we'll follow your lead.
Abokyo, I need you to run a replay.
Bring out moody jazz and
we'll get to work right away.
Yeah, sure thing.
You got it.
So where do you want to start?
Would when the soup was still
on the table be a good spot?
That's perfect.
What's up with you now?
Hey, the enemy's right over there!
Huh? Over there?
You mean inside the restaurant's bathroom?
I swear, you damn well better
have seen something this time!
Mm-hmm, I did!
Let's get on it then.
We'll settle the fight
with them here and now!
Come on, Giorno, let's move! Right.
Thanks for your help, Naraksha.
You've played your part beautifully.
I'm impressed.
Now your friends have no idea my stand
crush is quite a handy little helper.
Yes,
my stand talking mouth works wonders,
especially when it latches onto your tongue!
and forces you to say the exact
opposite of what you mean.
Well, my ish to kill isn't
going to scratch itself. Crazy.
So that's what all this
was about? Damn it!
Whoever this asshole is used me to get
the guys near the water one by one.
Nobody mocks me.
I'm not picking up on anything.
We have to figure out
this bastard's identity.
Moody Jess!
Transform into whoever was just in here
and start following their movements.
Narancia, finding the user with
Moody Jazz is a great plan,
but you can't go after them.
You're as good as dead in the water.
I'm going to have to bust my ass to keep
them as far as possible
from that death trap.
Hey, this must be it.
Moody Jazz is transforming into someone.
You have to get away from there.
Don't look in!
Hey!
Look over here, guys!
You won't believe what's in this bowl!
What?
You nasty little
get-it-together, would ya?
Get over here, Bakkyo!
I've got a present for ya!
Check the bowl for the surprise inside!
You've lost your mind!
Is this a new kind of fetish or something?
The only reason we're even
searching this place is
because you were yapping
on about seeing the enemy!
Just tell the damn truth
about what you saw!
I'm trying to tell -
Enough.
I'm over this.
Ucharati, I think all of this
was Narancia's imagination.
If we're gonna pursue whoever's after
us, we should go back to the table.
I suppose.
You need to get a frickin' grip, Narancia.
This kind of bullshit could derail
everything we've worked for.
Narancia, your finger, it's bleeding.
I think you may have cut it on something.
Here, let me stop the bleeding.
Katsune, you're gonna try
moving through my blood!
No, you can't come near me, Chorno!
Please, stay away!
Sounds good.
Thanks for offering.
Now I know something's not right.
What's going on inside of your mouth?
The enemy was messing
around with your tongue.
Is it connected?
Atta boy, Giorno.
I knew you'd pull through.
You're almost there.
You're so close to figuring
this whole thing out. Not good.
You're really bleeding.
We need to take care of this wound first.
Let me see.
No!
You can't touch my blood!
We need to hurry. Stop! Stay back!
Come on!
Little bummer!
Narancia, I haven't known you long,
but I can tell there's something
forcing you to act this way.
That must be the reason why you
can't give us a straight answer.
It's the enemy.
Thank goodness!
You finally figured it out!
I wonder if that stand left
something in your mouth.
That would explain all this.
This power makes you say the
opposite of what you mean. Yes!
That's it, Giorno!
Shit!
There's water leaking from the pipe!
Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
They are the passion.
They dare to tell us
what's bad and what's good!
Stand up, join us.
Come on, just see this alive!
We are the power.
Those days are future?
Cause we are the finest.
Just fighting for the right.
Let me go, I'm loving you.
I'm just a man, I'm just a man.
Let me go, I'm just a man.
Thank you.